Tim Moon

104/218 Bay road, Sandringham Mob: 0435 035 657

E-mail: tim.moon7@gmail.com

Profile

Qualified and skilled IT Support Analyst with 3 years experience and Software/Web Developer with 2 years experience, and extensive knowledge of Linux, Unix, Windows Server 2008/2012 (Active Directory, Group Policy, DHCP and DNS), Microsoft Office Suite, ITIL, Networking, Virtualization, SCCM, LYNC and SQL queries through the completion of several major projects with Bearing Point, Samsung and LG. Reliable and organized, with a positive attitude to work and learning.

Qualification

Master of Information Technology, High-achieving student The University of Melbourne

Key Skills

- Proven skills in Operating Systems such as Linux, UNIX, Windows XP/7/8 and Servers
- Sound knowledge of Microsoft Platforms (Office/Outlook) and Virtualisation (VSphere/HyperV)
- Sound knowledge of Programming; Ruby, Java, Jsp, C# and PHP
- Sound knowledge of Database Systems; MySQL, ORACLE and MS SQL
- Sound knowledge of Windows Server 2008 R2/2012 (Active Directory, DHCP, DNS, Group Policy, Printer Server), Proxy server and Microsoft Exchange Server
- Sound knowledge of CCNA Routing & Switching and ITIL
- Sound knowledge of Network; TCP/IP, VPN, LAN and WAN
- Sound knowledge of SCCM, Service-Now, JIRA, LYNC (Skype for Business) and Zeacom
- Proven skills in Backup system (CommVault) and Installation Hardware/Applications
- Sound knowledge of SAP (HR/SD/MM) and Salesforce CRM
- Strong problem solving and time management skills

Employment History

Field Service Desk Analyst

Feb 2016 - Current

BMS (Bristol-Myers Squibb)

Responsibilities:

- Handle the initial client contact at the Technology Service Desk via telephone, email, chat or portal
- Install Applications via SCCM
- Perform troubleshooting to resolve or escalate to the appropriate Tier 2/3 teams
- Log and manage incidents and requests
- Analyze and identify trends in issue reporting and devising preventive solutions
- Generate and update knowledge database
- Generate Daily, Weekly and Monthly reports

Graduate Infrastructure Engineer

Guild Group

Aug 2014 - Sep 2015

Responsibilities:

- Provided remote and onsite support
- Created and maintained Virtual Machines based on VSphere
- Managed Printer servers and Shared Network Drives
- Managed Group Policy, DHCP, DNS, VPN, SCCM and LYNC
- Configured Routers and Switches
- Worked with vendor support contacts
- Built Desktops/Laptops/Tablets and Install Applications
- Managed Proxy Server and Phone/Email gueue system (Zeacom)
- Developed documentations

IT Support (Internship)

Mar 2014 - June 2014

Logitrain, Melbourne

Responsibilities:

- Managed day-to-day administration functions utilizing Active Directory to facilitate password resets, establish email accounts, address log-in issues, manage group access
- Provided systems support, technical analysis, diagnosis, installation, maintenance, documentation and modification to the network
- Resolved incoming IT related support issues
- Installed and configured Cisco ISR 2811 routers and Cisco Catalyst 2960 switches

Steward (Casual)

Apr 2011 - Nov 2011

Park Hyatt Hotel, Melbourne

Responsibilities:

Assisted with food, set up and preparation for events

HR Administrator (IT)

2008

Korea Rail Network Authority, Korea

A Government authority with 1,600 employees constructing railways and station buildings and maintaining government rail assets

Responsibilities:

- Supported employees to use HR system and solved unexpected-problems
- Analyzed the relationship with SAP HR organization/education/promotion, and linkage with portal
- Managed large quantities of data and provided various reports as required using SQL queries
- Migrated previous data (staff positioning and salary data etc)

Software/Web Developer

2006 - 2007

Korea Rail Network Authority, Korea

Responsibilities:

- Supported employees how to use the new system (including training)
- Implemented HR/Payroll /Web Applications (based on Java/Jsp/Oracle/Apache Tomcat)

- Tested screens and data flow, and corrected errors
- Reported completion of development, including technical documentation

System Administrator

2004 - 2005

Korea Rail Network Authority, Korea

Responsibilities:

- Performed data backup of portal, groupware and enterprise applications and routine audits of systems and software
- Applied operating system updates and configured changes
- Supported IT problems solving including PCs, Laptops and printers
- Maintained Cisco routers and Firewall
- Documented manuals and configuration of the systems

Voluntary Experience

Sales Assistant Apr 2014 - Aug 2014

Salvation Army Salvos Store

Responsibilities:

Provided customer service

Participated in taking donation products and kept the store tidy and attractive

Computer Class Volunteer Tutor

June 2010 - Nov 2010

Hawthorn Community Education Centre

Responsibilities:

- Provided one-to-one training and support in using computers and MS-Office2007
- Supported participants and computer tutor

Education

Jul 2011 – Aug 2013 Master of Information Technology

The University of Melbourne

2010 Diploma of Information Technology (Software Development)

Swinburne University of Technology

1999 Bachelor of Engineering (Computer Science)

Chonnam National University, South Korea

Professional Training

Nov 2013 - June 2014 MCSA/CCNA/ITIL/Internship Logitrain Melbourne

2009 Oracle DBA & JAVA Professional Choongang Institute, Korea

2006 HR-mySAP ERP 5.0 / ABAP Workbench SAP Korea

Professional Licenses

2017 Certified as a CCNP ROUTE (19 Jan 2017)

Issued By: Cisco

2016 Certified as a CompTIA Linux+ [Powered by LPI] (28 Jan 2016) Certificate ID: G301D9S33DFEYRZG Issued By: CompTIA

2014 Certified as a ITIL Foundation 2011 (12 Feb 2014)
Certificate ID: GR750090199TM Issued By: Peoplecert

2014 Certified as a CCNA Routing & Switching (07 Feb 2014)

Certificate ID: 416778235512BQYG Issued By: Cisco

2014 Certified as a MCSA Windows Server 2012 (23 Jan 2014)

Certificate ID: E561-6269 Issued By: Microsoft

References

References available upon request